And today is fifty-six.
I talked yesterday about positioning today I wake up seeing this
here or passing a phone here that I won't show
the person's name and phone number,
but I was noticed by the Cora bank.
That's the point.
Zé on the corner will think you don't have the ability to bring him a plan
of action so the Cora bank notices you when you create your own box.
There is no need to prospect trying to be accepted.
Let's go.
It's open there,
okay?
I'll go see if there's a bro.
I need to buy truffles,
it's on holiday,
right?
Good thing the mall is open.
I have a lot of sore throat.
Old like that,
bro.
That's what you have for today.
Oops, okay, brother,
how are you?
It's better now,
damn it,
I like it.
You are the truffle seller.
That's what I put.
I'll follow you on the social network right here at the time.
What's the name of Brother Rafael Caio Rafael's pleasure,
oh Rafael give you a suggestion in a good Brother,
because you don't make a little shop here at Uber,
bro,
put some perfume here,
put the exhibitor here,
so go there and put a free sample,
a sampler for someone.
Feel the perfume on one of those.
I'm here, brother.
Suddenly I bought a perfume.
I sent the pix here.
Make it easy for people,
show your work.
Call,
like Rick Chester,
right?
You had the opportunity,
But how did he have it created?
Why doesn't you create your color?
Why don't we create?
We just stay there.
Oh,
the guy is an influencer.
Will be an influencer.
This is the call I mean,
anyone who is not seen is not remembered brother.
We have to create our own box.
Hug hooman we're together.
Got the trupa.
I didn't even see it.
I need to have something like this to remind me of so much going on.
It is important for us to organize our thoughts.
I could have done it yesterday,
saved I could have,
but I hesitated.
They are in time too.
It's 1 very important thing you know?
Bye bye girls.
Thanks.
Good weekend to you.
It saw?
And now replacement done.
Let's go my brother.
I commented that I have 1 idea way to share with you?
Instead of saying I prefer to put it into
practice but today is a public holiday.
I really hope this works out.
Is it on?